Register of the Papers of Judge John Paul 1930-1964
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
- CASES (Box 40)
  - Hypes v. Virginian Railway 1941 (Box 32)
  - Miscellaneous Case Material, Primarily Correspondence: H 1939-61, 8 folders (Box 32)
  - Ingram v. Greenleaf 1940-41 (Box 33)
  - ICC (Interstate Commerce Commission) Cases 1949 (Box 33)
  - Miscellaneous Case Material, Primarily Correspondence: I 1937-57 (Box 33)
  - Jacob v. Clearbrook Woolen 1955 (Box 33)
  - Jeffcoate v. Virginian Railway; Kelly v. Virginian Railway 1954 (Box 33)
  - Jewell Ridge Coal v. Early n.d. (Box 33)
  - Johnson v. Norfolk and Western 1958-59 (Box 33)
  - Johnson v. U.S. 1957-58 (Box 33)
  - Johnson Service v. J.M. Turner 1957-59 (Box 33)
  - Johnston v. Poirier 1958 (Box 33)
  - Jones v. Camp 1947-49 (Box 33)
  - Junk v. R.J. Reynolds Tobacco 1938 (Box 33)
  - Miscellaneous Case Material, Primarily Correspondence: J 1939-60, 4 folders (Box 33)
  - Kelly (Receiver of the Bank of Norton) v. Yeary 1936-37 (Box 34)
  - Kennett v. Early 1937-38 (Box 34)
  - Kilby v. School Board of Warren County 1958-62, 2 folders (Box 34)
  - Kirkland Distributing v. U.S. 1960 (Box 34)
  - Miscellaneous Case Material, Primarily Correspondence: K 1936-60, 4 folders (Box 34)
  - Lane Co. v. Coleman Furniture n.d. (Box 34)
  - Larson v. U.S. 1958 (Box 34)
  - Lawhorne v. Hercules Powder 1947 (Box 34)
  - Lemon v. U.S. b, 34 (Box b)
  - Lentz v. Riverton Lime 1938 (Box 34)
  - Letterman v. Norfolk & Western n.d. (Box 34)
  - London v. Hercules Powder 1947-51 (Box 34)
  - Long v. Dunkley 1938(?) (Box 34)
  - Lynchburg Traffic Bureau v. U.S. and Interstate Commerce Commission 1963-64 (Box 35)
  - Lyons v. Bailey and Safety Motor Transit 1936 (Box 35)
  - Miscellaneous Case Material, Primarily Correspondence: L 1936-62, 6 folders (Box 35)
  - Mackall v. U.S.; Pickett v. U.S. 1957-58 (Box 35)
  - MacCorkle v. U.S. 1933-34 (Box 35)
  - Maryland Casualty v. American Employers' Insurance 1953-54 (Box 35)
  - McAleenan v. Horning 1944-45 (Box 36)
  - McLendon v. Ramsey n.d. (Box 36)
  - , McElrath v. Industrial Rayon 1935-41 (Box 36)
  - Medford v. Ellis 1943 (Box 36)
  - Merck v. Mathieson 1955-58 (Box 36)
  - In re Merimac Anthracite Coal 1933-40 (Box 36)
  - Miles Laboratories v. Mick-or-Mack; Miles Laboratories v. Garland 1954-58 (Box 36)
  - Miller v. Harris n.d. (Box 36)
  - Miller v. South River Mining 1958-59 (Box 36)
  - Moffet v. [?] n.d. (Box 36)
  - Morris v. Camel; Vandiver v. Camel 1952 (Box 36)
  - Morrison v. U.S. 1959 (Box 37)
  - Myers v. American Well Works 1939-40 (Box 37)
  - Myers v. Mutual Benefit 1955 (Box 37)
  - Miscellaneous Case Material, Primarily Correspondence: M 1935-55, 4 folders (Box 37)
  - Miscellaneous Case Material, Primarily Correspondence: Mc 1935-62, 3 folders (Box 37)
  - Re: National Bank of Norton 1938 (Box 37)
  - National Fruit Product v. U.S. 1952 (Box 37)
  - National Labor Relations Board v. Ryder Tank Lines 1960-62 (Box 37)
  - National Toy and Tinsel v. Merimac Anthracite Coal 1941 (Box 37)
  - Nolan v. U.S. 1950 (Box 38)
  - Noland v. Wood Construction 1937-38 (Box 38)
  - Nonsuco v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue; San Vicente v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue 1956 (Box 38)
  - Nordstrom v. Firestone Tire and Rubber; Werkheiser v. Firestone Tire and Rubber 1950-51 (Box 38)
  - Norfolk Southern v. Roanoke Iron & Bridge Works n.d. (Box 38)
  - Norfolk and Western v. U.S. 1956 (Box 38)
  - Novocol Chemical v. Powers and Anderson 1942 (Box 38)
  - Miscellaneous Case Material, Primarily Correspondence: N 1932-63, 3 folders (Box 38)
  - In re Henry Charles O'Dell 1954-58 (Box 38)
  - Miscellaneous Case Material, Primarily Correspondence: O 1936-60, 3 folders (Box 38)
  - Pacific-Atlantic Steamship v. U.S. 1946-48 (Box 38)
  - Peck v. Norfolk and Western 1947-48 (Box 38)
  - Peeler v. Shell Union Oil 1938-40 (Box 38)
  - Penello v. Burlington Industries 1963 (Box 39)
  - Penello v. Local No. 980 1957 (Box 39)
  - Penello v. Roanoke Building & Construction Trades Council 1956 (Box 39)
  - Penny v. Alexandria Building Supplies 1951 (Box 39)
  - Peoples National Bank of Charlottesville v. U.S. 1954-56 (Box 39)
  - Pettry v. Lehigh Portland Cement 1956 (Box 39)
  - Poe v. U.S. 1936-40 (Box 39)
  - Poti-Port v. Federal Trade Commission 1962 (Box 39)
  - Power and Combustion v. Wilson Mandate 1962 (Box 39)
  - Pritchard v. Nelson 1942-44 (Box 39)
  - Proctor v. Biller 1957-58 (Box 39)
  - In re Production Credit Association 1959-60 (Box 39)
  - Prudential Insurance v. Cupp n.d. (Box 39)
  - Prudential Insurance v. Thomas 1960-61 (Box 39)
  - Pugh v. Lindsay n.d. (Box 39)
  - Pullman v. U.S. n.d. (Box 39)
  - Miscellaneous Case Material, Primarily Correspondence: P 1935-64, 7 folders (Box 39-40)
  - Miscellaneous Case Material, Primarily Correspondence: Q 1950-58 (Box 40)
  - Rachman v. Cohen 1956-60 (Box 40)
  - In re C. L. Radford 1956-57 (Box 40)
  - Railway Labor Executives Assn. v. U.S. 1962-64 (Box 40)
  - Rakes v. U.S. 1964 (Box 40)
  - Reasor v. Crum 1956 (Box 40)
  - , Redmond v. O'Sullivan Rubber 1950 (Box 40)
  - Richardson v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue 1956 (Box 40)
  - Richmond Sand and Gravel v. Motor Tug "Fisher" 1947-48 (Box 40)
  - Rickett v. Federal Roanoke Truck Sales 1951 (Box 40)
  - Ex parte E. J. Roberts 1944-50 (Box 40)
  - Robertson v. Norfolk and Western 1956-57 (Box 40)
  - Rodgers v. Irvine 1957-58 (Box 40)
  - Rogers v. Houff 1956 (Box 40)
  - Re: William Edward Ross 1946 (Box 41)
  - Rudisill v. Chesapeake and Ohio 1946-50 (Box 41)
  - Miscellaneous Case Material, Primarily Correspondence: R (6 folders) 1933-59 (Box-folder Box 41)
  - Sampsell, et al v. Casey Jones 1944-45 (Box-folder Box 41)
  - Saville v. U.S. n.d. (Box-folder Box 41)
  - Scott v. Norton Hardware n.d. (Box-folder Box 41)
  - Sechrist v. Dyke 1958 (Box-folder Box 41)
  - Shepard & Co. v. Agwilines 1942 (Box-folder Box 41)
  - Shepherd v. Mitchell 1956 (Box-folder Box 41)
  - Shreckhise v. Ritchie n.d. (Box-folder Box 41)
  - Silberstein v. Virginia State Lines 1958 (Box-folder Box 41)
  - Simmons v. Atlantis Greyhound 1947-48 (Box-folder Box 41)
  - Smallwood v. U.S. 1934-37 (Box-folder Box 41)
  - Smith v. Gay 1950-51 (Box-folder Box 41)
  - Smith v. National Fruit Products 1936-37 (Box-folder Box 42)
  - Smith v. U.S. 1950-51 (Box-folder Box 42)
  - Snead v. New York Central 1954-55 (Box-folder Box 42)
  - Standard Brands v. Eastern Shore Canning 1947-49 (Box-folder Box 42)
  - Stearn, et al. v. U.S. and ICC 1949 (Box-folder Box 42)
  - Steele v. Harry Hamrick and Hoover Lines 1937 (Box-folder Box 42)
  - Stephenson v. Equitable Life Assurance Society 1936-37 (Box-folder Box 42)
  - Sterrett v. Hirsh 1932-39 (Box-folder Box 42)
  - Stevens, et al. v. Howard D. Johnson Co. 1949-50 (Box-folder Box 42)
  - Straight Side Basket v. Berryville Basket 1933-36 (Box-folder Box 42)
  - Strong v. Cabell 1938-39 (Box-folder Box 42)
  - Sutton v. Hart n.d. (Box-folder Box 42)
  - Swanson v. Rector and Visitors of U.Va. 1950 (Box-folder Box 42)
  - Miscellaneous Case Material, Primarily Correspondence: S (11 folders) 1930-63 (Box-folder Box 42-44)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority v. Southern States Power n.d. (Box-folder Box 44)
  - Tiedman, et al. v. American Pigment; Tiedman, et al. v. Appalachian Electric 1952-57 (Box-folder Box 44)
  - Tilghman Moyer v. Pulaski National Bank 1938 (Box-folder Box 44)
  - Tomlinson v. U.S. 1935-40 (Box-folder Box 44)
  - Tompkins v. Tompkins 1934-36 (Box-folder Box 44)
  - Tucker v. Fowlkes n.d. (Box-folder Box 44)
  - Miscellaneous Case Material, Primarily Correspondence: T (6 folders) 1936-64 (Box-folder Box 44-45)
  - U.S. v. Appalachian Electric (3 folders) n.d. (Box-folder Box 45)
  - U.S. v. H.C. Bolling n.d. (Box-folder Box 45)
  - U.S. v. Boone n.d. (Box-folder Box 45)
  - U.S. v. Cases of Early June Peas (4 separate suits) 1942-44 (Box-folder Box 45)
  - U.S. v. Chesapeake and Ohio 1941-44 (Box-folder Box 45)
  - U.S. v. Coffman 1940-43 (Box-folder Box 45)
  - U.S. v. Craddock-Terry Shoe Corp. n.d. (Box-folder Box 45)
  - U.S. v. Danton 1950-53 (Box-folder Box 45)
  - U.S. v. Fletcher 1948-54 (Box-folder Box 45)
  - U.S. v. Franklin 1945-47 (Box-folder Box 45)
  - U.S. v. Gochenaur n.d. (Box-folder Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Hall 1954 (Box-folder Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Harnsberger 1952 (Box-folder Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Lee Bank and Trust 1934-38 (Box-folder Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Leftwick n.d. (Box-folder Box 46)
  - U.S. v. McWilliams (sediton case) 1944 (Box-folder Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Gomery Granville Miller 1940-41 (Box-folder Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Mucherino 1962-63 (Box-folder Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Nowlin 1938-39 (Box-folder Box 46)
  - U.S. v. M.G. O'Farrell 1954 (Box-folder Box 46)
  - U.S. v. One Chevrolet Truck n.d. (Box-folder Box 46)
  - U.S. v. One Ford Coach Automobile n.d. (Box-folder Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Perkins 1958 (Box-folder Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Pittsburgh Plate Glass 1957-59 (Box-folder Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Roanoke Motor n.d. (Box-folder Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Saglietto; U.S. v. Ravasini (2 folders) 1941-42 (Box-folder Box 46)
  - U.S. v. St. Clair 1944-55 (Box-folder Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Shively (Franklin County liquor conspiracy case) 1936-37 (Box-folder Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Showalter 1952(?) (Box-folder Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Showker 1950-51; 1953 (Box-folder Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Shrout 1958 (Box-folder Box 47)
  - U.S. v. Smith 1958 (Box-folder Box 47)
  - U.S. v. Sutherland 1937 (Box-folder Box 47)
  - U.S. v. Town of Waynesboro 1947-48 (Box-folder Box 47)
  - U.S. v. Wenzel 1962-63 (Box-folder Box 47)
  - U.S. v. Wolcott 1943-44 (Box-folder Box 47)
  - U.S. v. Wolfe 1952-53 (Box-folder Box 47)
  - U.S. for the use of Noland Co. v. Worsham and American Surety 1935-37 (Box-folder Box 47)
  - Miscellaneous Case Material, Primarily Correspondence: U 1936-60 (Box-folder Box 47)
  - Vaughan v. Ellis[?] n.d. (Box-folder Box 47)
  - Vaughan v. Miller n.d. (Box-folder Box 47)
  - Vaughn v. Virginian Railway 1942-44 (Box-folder Box 47)
  - Vecellio v. Bopst 1937-38 (Box-folder Box 47)
  - Virginia Stage Lines v. U.S. 1942 (Box-folder Box 47)
  - Vroon v. Templin 1960 (Box-folder Box 47)
  - Miscellaneous Case Material, Primarily Correspondence: V (1934-64) 1934-64 (Box-folder Box 47)
  - Wachter v. Palumbo n.d. (Box-folder Box 47)
  - Walker v. Farley 1958-63 (Box-folder Box 47)
  - Walker v. Floyd County School Board 1960-64 (Box-folder Box 47)
  - Wallinger v. Certainteed Products n.d. (Box-folder Box 48)
  - Weakley v. U.S. 1945-47 (Box-folder Box 48)
  - Weaver v. Marcus 1947-48 (Box-folder Box 48)
  - Wedge v. Titus Nursery 1934-40 (Box-folder Box 48)
  - Weeks v. Weeks 1962-63 (Box-folder Box 48)
  - Weissman v. Davies 1951-53 (Box-folder Box 48)
  - Werth v. Williams 1952(?) (Box-folder Box 48)
  - West v. Chesapeake & Ohio 1951-52 (Box-folder Box 48)
  - Wheeling Steel v U.S. 1936-38 (Box-folder Box 48)
  - Whitlock v. Lambert 1954 (Box-folder Box 48)
  - Whittaker v. Fossan 1960-62 (Box-folder Box 48)
  - Wiley & Sons v. U.S. and ICC 1949 (Box-folder Box 48)
  - Williams v. Nichols 1959 (Box-folder Box 48)
  - Williams v. Shope 1938 (Box-folder Box 48)
  - Willis v. Dermis n.d. (Box-folder Box 48)
  - Wood v. U.S. n.d. (Box-folder Box 48)
  - Woods v. Forman; U.S. v. Kessler; U.S. v. Lynskey 1949 (Box-folder Box 48)
  - Wright v. U.S. 1952-56 (Box-folder Box 48)
  - Wyant v. Caldwell 1936-40 (Box-folder Box 48)
  - Miscellaneous Case Material, Primarily Correspondence: W (7 folders) 1935-62 (Box-folder Box 49)
  - Miscellaneous Case Material, Primarily Correspondence: X,Y,Z 1936-63 (Box-folder Box 49)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Motions, Pleadings & Orders: A -Z (57 folders) n.d. (Box-folder Box 50-57)
  - Miscellaneous Case Notes: Handwritten Notes on Testimony taken from Bench (41 folders) 1933-61 (Box-folder Box 58-60)
  - Miscellaneous Unknown Cases n.d. (Box-folder Box 61)
  - Miscellaneous Criminal Cases: Correspondence, Motions, Pleadings & Orders (19 folders) 1939-61 (Box-folder Box 61)
- BANKRUPTCY CASES
  - Administrative: Correspondence (6 folders) 1928-64 (Box-folder Box 62)
  - Admin.: Referees in Bankruptcy -- Appointments (5 folders) 1931-62 (Box-folder Box 62-63)
  - Admin.: Referees in Bankrutcy --Expense Accounts (12 folders) 1934-59 (Box-folder Box 63-64)
  - Admin.: Referees in Bankruptcy -- Map 1946 (Box-folder Box 64)
  - Admin.: Referees in Bankruptcy -- Reports for Judicial Conferences 1947;1954;1958 (Box-folder Box 64)
  - Edna E. Allen 1932 (Box-folder Box 65)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence: A (2 folders) 1933-59 (Box-folder Box 65)
  - Charles Barksdale & E.C. Buck 1933 (Box-folder Box 65)
  - Beaver Products Co. (3 folders) 1932-34 (Box-folder Box 65)
  - Boothe Drug Store n.d. (Box-folder Box 65)
  - Henry Potter Britt n.d. (Box-folder Box 65)
  - James H. Burnley 1947(?) (Box-folder Box 65)
  - Charles B. Burruss 1933 (Box-folder Box 65)
  - Bush & Hancock, Inc. 1933 (Box-folder Box 65)
  - Annie L. Butler n.d. (Box-folder Box 65)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence: B (6 folders) 1932-61 (Box-folder Box 65-66)
  - Samuel Caldwell 1945(?) (Box-folder Box 66)
  - Carden & Carden n.d. (Box-folder Box 66)
  - Central States Electric Corporation (4 folders) 1930-45 (Box-folder Box 66)
  - Hallie J. Cobb 1933-34 (Box-folder Box 67)
  - Isabel Cochrane 1937(?) (Box-folder Box 67)
  - Courtroy & Courtroy 1958(?) (Box-folder Box 67)
  - David Morse Crabtree 1944-45 (Box-folder Box 67)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence: C (5 folders) 1932-59 (Box-folder Box 67)
  - E.L. Davis, trading as Perm-Davis Coal Co. n.d. (Box-folder Box 67)
  - James Davis 1949(?) (Box-folder Box 67)
  - Dixie Splint Coal Co. 1937-40 (Box-folder Box 67)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence: D (3 folders) 1932-63 (Box-folder Box 67-68)
  - Levi Hamilton Easter 1934-43 (Box-folder Box 68)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence: E 1932-38 (Box-folder Box 68)
  - W.F. Flanagan 1932-34 (Box-folder Box 68)
  - Fuller Drug Co. 1933-34 (Box-folder Box 68)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence: F (2 folders) 1932-59 (Box-folder Box 68)
  - George Garber 1936(?) (Box-folder Box 68)
  - S.A. Garrison, Inc. 1956-57 (Box-folder Box 68)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Reocords & Correspondence: G (2 folders) 1928-59 (Box-folder Box 68)
  - Hailey Mercantile Co. 1932-34 (Box-folder Box 69)
  - William Holloway 1937(?) (Box-folder Box 69)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence: H (5 folders) 1928-59 (Box-folder Box 69)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence: I 1933-36;1949;1954 (Box-folder Box 69)
  - Vivian D. Johnston 1932-33 (Box-folder Box 69)
  - Arthur G. Jones Woolen Mills Corp. 1930-60 (Box-folder Box 69)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence: J (2 folders) 1932-59 (Box-folder Box 69-70)
  - Reba B. Koontz 1933 (Box-folder Box 70)
  - Charles Eugene Kyle 1935-36 (Box-folder Box 70)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence: K (2 folders) 1932-59 (Box-folder Box 70)
  - W.D. Lawton n.d. (Box-folder Box 70)
  - Lincoln Industries 1958(?) (Box-folder Box 70)
  - James Stoker Long 1938(?) (Box-folder Box 70)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence: L (3 folders) 1932-59 (Box-folder Box 70)
  - Lloyd Marcus 1933 (Box-folder Box 70)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence: Mc (2 folders) 1934-59 (Box-folder Box 70)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence: M (4 folders) 1930-62 (Box-folder Box 70-71)
  - National Manufacturing Co. 1958(?) (Box-folder Box 71)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence: N (2 folders) 1934-61 (Box-folder Box 71)
  - French Oakes n.d. (Box-folder Box 71)
  - Robert Osborn n.d. (Box-folder Box 71)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence: O (2 folders) 1933-60 (Box-folder Box 71)
  - George William Paynter 1937 (Box-folder Box 71)
  - Pride of Virginia Poultry Corp. 1959-61 (Box-folder Box 71)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence: P (3 folders) 1932-59 (Box-folder Box 71)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence: Q 1934-41 (Box-folder Box 71)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence: R (3 folders) 1932-59 (Box-folder Box 71)
  - Shawker Bros., Inc. 1950(?) (Box-folder Box 71)
  - Sidney's Incorporated (3 folders) 1932-34 (Box-folder Box 71-72)
  - Ansel Solenberger 1959(?) (Box-folder Box 72)
  - James Luther Sturgill 1956 (Box-folder Box 72)
  - J.C. Sutherland 1939-41 (Box-folder Box 72)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence: S (6 folders) 1932-60 (Box-folder Box 72)
  - Walter Thompson 1943(?) (Box-folder Box 72)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence: T (2 folders) 1932-59 (Box-folder Box 72)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence: U 1939-58 (Box-folder Box 72)
  - Virginia Hot Springs Co. (6 folders) 1939-54 (Box-folder Box 72-73)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence: V (2 folders) 1934-59 (Box-folder Box 73)
  - Robert Irwin Winn 1939 (Box-folder Box 73)
  - Jesse C. Wood 1942-44 (Box-folder Box 73)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence: W (3 folders) 1932-61 (Box-folder Box 73)
  - Harding Yates 1941-42 (Box-folder Box 73)
  - James Elmer Yount 1941 (Box-folder Box 73)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence: Y-Z 1933-59 (Box-folder Box 73)
- SECTION 75 BANKRUPTCY CASES
  - Individual and Business Cases
  - Administrative: Conciliation Commissioners (6 folders) 1934-50 (Box-folder Box 74)
  - Admin.: Conciliation Commissioners -- Forms n.d. (Box-folder Box 74)
  - Admin.: Conciliation Commissioners -- Record of Appointments 1934-49 (Box-folder Box 74)
  - Admin.: Correspondence Regarding Statute 1934-43 (Box-folder Box 74)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence -- A 1934-36 (Box-folder Box 75)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence -- B 1934-43 (Box-folder Box 75)
  - Oder P. Carter (2 folders) 1940-51 (Box-folder Box 75)
  - Mary V. Chaney (2 folders) 1937-48 (Box-folder Box 75)
  - Lucy Conrad (2 folders) 1935-37 (Box-folder Box 75)
  - James L. Cunningham 1934-35 (Box-folder Box 75)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence -- C 1935-42 (Box-folder Box 75)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence -- D 1934-40 (Box-folder Box 75)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence -- E 1939-59 (Box-folder Box 75)
  - James Flanagan 1935-37 (Box-folder Box 76)
  - Sallie T. Frazier 1937 (Box-folder Box 76)
  - S. Grat Gillespie 1934-36 (Box-folder Box 76)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence -- G 1934-43 (Box-folder Box 76)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence -- H 1934-43 (Box-folder Box 76)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence -- J 1935 (Box-folder Box 76)
  - Nannie P. Large 1936-38 (Box-folder Box 76)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence -- L 1935-50 (Box-folder Box 76)
  - Elizabeth Massey 1937(?) (Box-folder Box 76)
  - Meyers & Sifford 1934-35 (Box-folder Box 76)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence -- M (2 folders) 1934-40 (Box-folder Box 77)
  - James R. Nichols (4 folders) 1934-37 (Box-folder Box 77)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence -- O 1935;1942 (Box-folder Box 77)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence -- Q 1934-38 (Box-folder Box 77)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence -- R 1934-48 (Box-folder Box 77)
  - J.E. Sheets 1935-39 (Box-folder Box 77)
  - W.J. Shelburne 1936-38 (Box-folder Box 77)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence -- S 1934-36 (Box-folder Box 77)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence -- T 1934-49 (Box-folder Box 78)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence -- U 1935-36 (Box-folder Box 78)
  - C.D. Vernon 1935-37 (Box-folder Box 78)
  - Annie R. Wharton (2 folders) 1935-44 (Box-folder Box 78)
  - D.H. Whitmore 1942-45 (Box-folder Box 78)
  - G. Frank Wolfe 1937(?) (Box-folder Box 78)
  - Robert Page Wright 1937 (Box-folder Box 78)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence -- W (2 folders) 1934-43 (Box-folder Box 78)
  - Unknown Case n.d. (Box-folder Box 78)
- CONDEMNATION CASES
  - Administrative Matters (7 folders) 1934-60 (Box-folder Box 79)
  - Admin.: Condemnation Procedure, Rule 71A -- Correspondence (2 folders) 1947-56 (Box-folder Box 79)
  - Admin.: Condemnation Rule -- Article by John Paul for Iowa Law Review and related correspondence 1957-60 (Box-folder Box 80)
  - Admin.: Rules of Civil Procedure for the District Courts -- Preliminary Drafts of Proposed Amendments and Subsequent Reports 1944-51 (Box-folder Box 80)
  - George Abbitt Land (Buckingham and Appomattox) 1941 (Box-folder Box 80)
  - E.P. Akers' Heirs' Land (Montgomery) 1942 (Box-folder Box 80)
  - Annie C. Alexander Land (Pulaski) (3 folders) 1942-46 (Box-folder Box 80)
  - Agnes M. Altizer Land (Pulaski) 1942-43 (Box-folder Box 80)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence -- A 1935-42 (Box-folder Box 80)
  - Edgar W. Bell Land (Pulaski) 1941-42 (Box-folder Box 80)
  - J.R. Bentley Land (Pulaski) 1943 (Box-folder Box 80)
  - C.A. and J.A. Bloyd Land (Bath) 1937-39 (Box-folder Box 80)
  - A.L. Browne Land (Rappahannock) 1937-38 (Box-folder Box 80)
  - Lawrence A. Buzzard Land (Bath) 1932-38 (Box-folder Box 80)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence -- B 1940-51 (Box-folder Box 80)
  - Bessie A. Caldwell Land (Craig and Roanoke) 1943-51 (Box-folder Box 81)
  - Willie Ann Cale Land (Augusta and Bath) 1941-45 (Box-folder Box 81)
  - Roy M. Cash Land (Amherst) 1941-45 (Box-folder Box 81)
  - F.J. Chapman Land (Bedford and Roanoke) 1937-38 (Box-folder Box 81)
  - Clifton Forge National Bank Land (Botetourt) 1936-40 (Box-folder Box 81)
  - J.A. Cline Land (Alleghany) 1937-40 (Box-folder Box 81)
  - L.M. Crabtree Land (Pulaski) 1941-44 (Box-folder Box 81)
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co. Land (Craig and Giles) 1936-38 (Box-folder Box 81)
  - J.W. Crouse Land (Carroll and Grayson) 1939-40 (Box-folder Box 81)
  - Eldon K. Crowder Land (Alleghany) 1940-42 (Box-folder Box 81)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence -- C 1933-50 (Box-folder Box 81)
  - Joseph Darnell Land (Rappahannock) 1938-42 (Box-folder Box 81)
  - John L. Dickinson, Trustee (Craig and Montgomery) 1937-38 (Box-folder Box 81)
  - Douthat Land Co. (Alleghany and Bath) 1937-40 (Box-folder Box 81)
  - Walden Dudley Estate (Pulaski) 1940-60 (Box-folder Box 81)
  - M.L. Earman Land (Appomattox) 1936 (Box-folder Box 81)
  - F.C. Eckmann Land (Bath) 1938-39 (Box-folder Box 81)
  - Edgar S. Edwill Land (Cumberland) 1941-42 (Box-folder Box 81)
  - Nancy A. Elgin Land (Patrick) 1950-51 (Box-folder Box 81)
  - Walter M. Elmore Land (Craig) 1949-51 (Box-folder Box 81)
  - England, Walton & Co. Land (Rockingham) 1935-43 (Box-folder Box 81)
  - Charles F. Fielder Land (Grayson) 1936-37 (Box-folder Box 82)
  - Forest Lumber Co. Land (Highland) 1936 (Box-folder Box 82)
  - J.E. Fowler Land (Clarke and Loudoun) 1957-58 (Box-folder Box 82)
  - Minnie B. Fudge Estate (Alleghany) 1958-60 (Box-folder Box 82)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Reports & Correspondence -- D-F 1936-47 (Box-folder Box 82)
  - Bertha B. Galbraith Land (Botetourt and Craig) 1936-39 (Box-folder Box 82)
  - Claude E. Garrett Land (Washington) 1950-52 (Box-folder Box 82)
  - Gates, Trustee (Smyth and Washington) 1927-38 (Box-folder Box 82)
  - T.M. Gathright (Alleghany and Botetourt 1938-39 (Box-folder Box 82)
  - Gilpin Estate Trustees & Nettie C. Wiley Land (Clarke and Loudoun) 1955-62 (Box-folder Box 82)
  - Girard Trust Co. Land (Craig) 1937-38 (Box-folder Box 82)
  - Edna M. Givens Land (Craig) 1939 (Box-folder Box 82)
  - Gochenour Land (Warren) 1934 (Box-folder Box 82)
  - Annie Burke Good Land (Rockingham) 1949-50 (Box-folder Box 82)
  - Mary Kate Gough Land (Scott) 1937-38 (Box-folder Box 82)
  - Hagen Estate (Scott) 1935-43 (Box-folder Box 82)
  - K.A. Harman Land (Rockingham) 1933-37 (Box-folder Box 82)